[{"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["parsley", "basil", "dill", "mayonnaise"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["inch", "ounce", "centimeter", "yard"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["tyre", "steering wheel", "engine", "car"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["tulip", "rose", "bud", "daisy"], "answer": "c"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["rye", "sourdough", "pumpernickel", "loaf"], "answer": "a"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["guitar", "flute", "violin", "cello"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["dodge", "flee", "duck", "avoid"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["branch", "dirt", "leaf", "root"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["street", "freeway", "interstate", "expressway"], "answer": "a"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["heading", "body", "letter", "closing"], "answer": "c"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["tape", "twine", "cord", "yarn"], "answer": "a"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["leopard", "cougar", "elephant", "lion"], "answer": "c"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["couch", "rug", "table", "chair"], "answer": "b"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["cornea", "retina", "pupil", "vision"], "answer": "d"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["noun", "preposition", "punctuation", "adverb"], "answer": "c"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["book", "index", "glossary", "chapter"], "answer": "a"}, {"question": "Which word does NOT belong with the others?", "options": ["unimportant", "trivial", "insignificant", "familiar"], "answer": "d"}]
